All right!
Whoa!
I'm scared!
I'm okay! I'm okay!
Ready?
♪♪
Good morning!
It's a beautiful day!
It's raining!
Where are we?
Pearl's grandfather's house.
It's a stranger's house.
This is Pearl's grandpa's house.
You're all so ugly.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Yes, please give me the correct answer.
Yes, this is
I used a small house in the autumn rain.
Who's that?
Mr. Akisame?
It's not Mr. Akisame. It's Autumn rain.
Autumn?
It's not Autumn rain.
It's autumn rain.
The small house of autumn rain in the hot spring and
It is a combination of a small private house and a camp.
It's a facility called Kominpingu.
Kominpingu?
Yes, that is correct.
Glad to hear it.
Yes, that's right.
I've come all this way, so I thought I'd enjoy it.
Yes!
Thank you very much.
But it doesn't end here, suddenly Gundan!
Everyone has been saying since this morning that they were a little hungry.
I'm hungry!
Hungry is all I can say.
I thought I'd let you all cook today.
Oh!
First time.
Oh, my gosh! I've never seen you cook live before.
No! I've only seen the finished product.
So it's a question of how much of it is him cooking.
I see.
It's no use if all 9 of us cook together.
It's no use!
It can't be helped!
No choice!
We'll draw lots and divide into 3 teams of 3 people each.
First of all, we will draw lots one by one.
After drawing lots, don't show them to anyone.
Only for the camera.
When everyone has finished drawing, please announce it.
Now, let's have the teams draw their lots.
Risako, let's go!
Risako!
I'll draw lots.
Not a chance.
What will it be?
Let's see what will come out.
Ah! It's good.
Here it is.
Here we go.
Eyebrows are nice.
I think they're great.
If you don't have eyebrows, you're gonna sweat 'em out.
I'm a lion.
Okay, I'm going to pull it out.
I put it in there.
I knew it. It's Grandpa's house.
Oh, you put it in there for Grandpa?
Please use it, I promise.
You know, I usually do that.
It's a little YouTuber fun.
Jansan, ah, that's cute!
You'll get it back when the clothes come on.
What do you think?
Who's going to stop me?
Okay, I'm ready.
Yes!
My survivor!
Dame!
Okay, let's hear it from Tachibana-san!
I am a pig!
I'm a penguin!
And before that, a duck!
Are we all different?
Not all of you?
Yuna, you're a duck!
I'm a duck!
I'm a heart!
I'm a penguin!
What? Where are you?
I am a pig!
My name is Pig!
I'm a penguin!
Let's split up into teams, please.Roughly, please split up into teams.
Yes, so I've asked you to divide into three teams.
I can't help it if you all cook under the same conditions.
It's no use!
I've prepared today's budget for 1,000 yen, 2,000 yen, and 3,000 yen.
So, three representatives from each team will now draw an envelope at random.
Three representatives from each team will draw an envelope at random.
Shall we go?
I'm going!
Please!
Okay, come on, come on!
Let's play rock-paper-scissors!
First, goo, then rock-paper-scissors!
That's it!
Good luck!
Cotton!
Yes!
Here we go!
Nice! Yeah!
Yeah! There they go! Next!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes! Go back once!
Yes! Then check inside!
Quick!
Whoa!
Wow!
Yes!
That's 2,000 yen.
So-so, so-so, but 1,000 yen
1,000 yen.
You were the first to get hit.
What?
I've got a real 10 yen.
So, on a budget...
The dish you're going to make is...
Curry.
Oh, wow!
Congratulations!
Are you okay? Don't you want some kunashi?
Are you okay? It's the countryside team.
So, about the curry, there's only one rule.
You have to add one originality to the curry.
I see.
Two other teams will eat it and give it a score.
Ten points for taste, ten points for originality.
And lastly, I'm counting on you all to come up with a miracle. 10 points.
Miracle?
So the maximum score will be 60 points.
The team that scores 60 points in the competition will get to clean up after everything you've cooked today.
Yes!
I'm sorry!
So, with all the noise...
I can't open it anymore.
It's too soon.
Okay, so...
Since we've come all the way to Akiyu today
I came to a famous saucer bar in Akiyu
Saichi, a famous saucer bar in Akiyu!
Ohagi (rice balls) are so delicious!
They are so famous for their o-hagi!
Hee...
They are so delicious!
But what I'm making today is curry!
But with this money, we can use the extra money for dessert.
That's originality!
Oh, I see.
First, let's head to Saichi and do some shopping!
Let's go!
So, we have arrived at Saechi!
Yes, we, you know, we would like to buy within the money, 3000 yen!
Really nice!
Really, there is fortune in leftovers, just like others.
Moreover, look at this.
Potatoes, eggplants, onions, and carrots are all here!
They're all here!
As expected, I'd like to take a look at the inside too, and decide!
Let's go!
Snowblood and milk?
I don't have any, but I've seen that it's easy to make.
Let's mix it up anyway, shall we?
But I'll do the curry anyway, and I might have some extra money.
Sure thing.
Toro puree, mixed cheese, or one?
I guess so.
I'll add cheese for now.
Thank you, Kurt.
You are very famous, aren't you?
Famous.
If you have any left over, bring some good luck.
Yes, I guess so.
First of all, what if it's a cow or a pig?
Half a cow.
I'm half cow, half pig.
But one moment I'm going to betray the pig.
Everybody, cover your pig ears.
Okay, okay.I get it.
This one!
It's a pig.
A pig.
Curry is a pig?
Yes, it's pork.
The more meat, the better.
But I think it tastes better with more meat.
Do you think everyone uses it?
Certainly.
But there's also the strategy of making them sell out.
Dare to sell out.
We are a pork team, so we have to put meat in our curry.
So, we make them sell out.
For curry.
Here it is. Nothing left.
I want to eat.
I am conflicted.
And it comes in three flavors.
It looks delicious.
I'll just have to eat it.
If you don't have a budget.
How much is it now?
I'm sure it's not too much to ask.
You don't have to go over 3,000 yen.
Is it 1,000 yen?
Don't say that.
It's about 1,000 yen.
No, no, no.
We have to use what we can.
Katayaki fries.
There are more things I want to buy personally.
Hinano, I have kataage fries with black pepper.
What should I do with them?
Um, how about hamburger steak curry?
Hamburg? That sounds good.
Do you have ice cream?
I'll get ice cream.
Okay, I'm going to the press conference now.
This is what it looks like.
I bought a lot of ice cream.
Ta-da!
I'm so excited!
We've arrived at 1 year old!
I haven't had a meal in about a year, so I haven't decided yet.
I'm going to make a doria... what should I make?
But it doesn't look like a normal curry anymore.
We're aiming for something a little off the beaten track from curry rice.
It's 2,000 yen, right?
It doesn't say "curry" but this is the curry section.
Neither one of us likes pumpkin.
If it's too much, we'll ask for ingredients locally.
I'm on top of it.
Grad school's here.
I want some.
I've got all the ingredients for curry. I'm making offal.
I want peaches.
I want some.
Dead end of the year.
Can we go?
Can we?
I think I'll have the butter chicken curry.
Butter chicken curry?
Butter chicken curry is fine.
We have orchids, so I'll buy orchids.
Yay.
I want cheese.
This is good, isn't it?
Peaches are softer.
I'll put peach meat.
Chicken curry.
Anything is fine as long as it's made with curry.
Originality and miracles.
Miracle?
It's a miracle.
Miracles are impossible?
What can't you do?
It's a two-person show.
I'm sorry, sir.
Did you eat the melon bread?
It's okay.
Yura went to get something.
She didn't come back.
I want to buy some o-hagi.
Everyone likes o-hagi, so I asked if you'd put o-hagi on it.
Can you serve o-hagi separately?
Someone try.
Can I?
What?
It's what they asked for.
I'll take the liberty of doing this.
I want to eat it.
You can't just come in here and not buy this.
Oh, here it is!
I'm going to put this on curry.
Ew!
What are you going to do if you don't eat this?
What are you doing here if you don't buy this?
That's right.I know.
People start not buying this.
Then let's do that.
OK.
Here's what we bought
Looks delicious
Here... the "o-hagi" is trying to be a miracle!
What originality!
Okay, please!
Please!
So I'd like to pay the bill.
I'm off!
I don't think we can make a good curry if we don't save our power after all!
Power.
Spice for us.
Okay, I'll do it.
Let's buy something to eat
Less than 450 yen.
Yay!
I want o-hagi.
Let's get some o-hagi.
What flavor do you like?
Sesame.
Okay.
Can I have this one?
Seventy-five yen.
You want some potato chips or something?
I like black pepper on my potato chips.
Oh, that's good.
I like that one.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
OK. OK.
Here we are.
We're here.
Here we are. Knock-knock.
They came in the middle of the road.
It was raining the last time I was here, so I've only seen them in the middle of getting wet.
Today, too.
It's wet.
Are you depressed?
But you know what? I'm doing fine. I'm shopping.
It's only 1,000 yen.
That's right.
We can do it. We can do it.
We can do it.
Let's go for it, RMK.
Yeah. - Yeah.
RMK.
Let's go for it.
Okay, let's go.
Director Lu.
There's a lot of stuff here.
What do you wanna make?
I think we should start with this.
I think we'll go with doria.
Doria?
Yes, and I think we can make it differently.
Okay.
Oh, that's good.
Is this good?
Yeah, they're good.
There's two in the bag.
Get it.
What do you want?
What do you like?
You can both get two kinds.
Two kinds?
What do you like?
Maybe I like something.
I kind of like it.
I know you do.
Of course you do.
You got any cheap ones?
No.
It was a no-circle place for us.
That's what we'll put in there.
Okay, let's just use this cylinder.
All right.
Are you sure you don't need a miracle?
We need a miracle.
I want to buy something.
I want to buy some chips.
You want some chips?
Yeah.
The kind with the inagi inside.
Consommé.
You want some consommé in your white sauce?
We don't have consommé. Consommé.
Maybe some chocolate barley?
I'd like to.
Chocolate barley.
It's good. It's good.
You want some?
Let's put it in.
That's the spirit.This is momentum.
All right.
I'm scared.
The chocolate's melting. I can't do it anymore.
Ready?
Go, go, go, captain.
What do we do now?
He says we win.
Can we just take the momentum?
You're giving me the surprise of my life.
Just take it.
Thank you. - You're welcome.
Welcome back.
It's cheese.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's got an almond texture.
It's good.
You want some?
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, I'll get a penlight.
We won.
Yay!
So, is that it for the shopping?
We're done.
Okay, we'll go with this menu.
Okay.
I'm off to the cash register.
I'm off.
Wow!
What's with that "netya" sound?